[Music]
I have heard acaden is hidden in this
industry uh which is focusing on
Microsoft Erp system Solutions I think
if I if I amward with this company I can
become a better person and uh a powerful
person I say during my last job I gained
my experiences in this wood industry I
got this U membership of the Microsoft
Thailand program with aagen I can take a
lot of courses to becom a good business
Central consultant so that would not
take much long time and I think I can
use this software to help my customers
to dealing with their problems so that
was why I really wanted to be a
consultant team members was was was
really helpful to me and uh even the
upper management they makes me feel that
the acad is very big family with full of
love and understanding it was a really
good choice to start the career here by
academ personally I'm very interested in
the Erp solutions nurs for the wood
industry that's why I want to work in
academy so in my leisure time I would
drive my car to different places in
German and in Europe and take beautiful
photographs I would spend also much more
time with my
family to be one of this program means a
lot to me I am looking forward to
growing up with acaden as a business
Central
consultant